Guide to the American Civil Liberties Union of North Carolina Records, 1960-2020; 1960-ongoing and undated RL.00012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Executive Director Office Series, 1965-2001 and undated, 90 boxes
  - 1980s Files Subseries, 1980-1990
    - 1983-1986 Executive Office Files, 1971-1986
      - Correspondence Files, 1973-1986:
        - Letters to attorneys, 1982 (Box 41)
        - Letters from attorneys and memos, 1983 (Box 41)
        - CLU miscellaneous data and correspondence, 1982 (Box 41)
        - CLU correspondence re: other publications, 1982 (Box 42)
        - Letters from attorneys, 1985 (Box 42)
        - Memorandums from attorneys, 1985 (Box 42)
        - Rejections for assistance or legal aid, 1985 (Box 42)
        - NCCLU requesting assistance, 1985 (Box 42)
        - Memoranda from attorneys, 1984 (Box 42)
        - Rejections for assistance or legal aid, 1984 (Box 42)
        - Requests for assistance, 1984, 2 folders (Box 42)
        - Letters from attorneys, 1984 (Box 42)
        - Cooperating attorney correspondence (Box 42)
        - CLU rejections for assistance or legal aid, 1981 (Box 43)
        - Letters from attorneys, 1981 (Box 43)
        - Letters to attorneys, 1981 (Box 43)
        - CLU miscellaneous data and correspondence, 1981 (Box 43)
        - Advice and opinions, 1981 (Box 43)
        - CLU requests for assistance, 1980 (Box 43)
        - Rejections for assistance and/or legal aid, 1980 (Box 43)
        - Letters from attorneys, 1980 (Box 43)
        - Letters to attorneys, 1980 (Box 43)
        - Correspondence re: liberty, 1980 [the newsletter?] (Box 43)
        - Advice and opinions (requests and answers), 1980 (Box 43)
        - NCCLU Legal Foundation, Inc., correspondence, reports, etc. (Box 43)
        - Requesting assistance, 1986 (Box 43)
        - NCCLU: Rejections, 1986 (Box 43)
        - General Correspondence, 1986 (Box 43)
        - CLU correspondence, 1986 (Box 43)
        - Requests for aid, 1980-1981, 3 folders (Box 43)
        - Misc. legal correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 44)
        - CLU miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 44)
        - Norman B. Smith, General CLU correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 44)
        - Misc. correspondence, 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - George Gardner, CLU general correspondence (Box 44)
        - ACLU correspondence and memos, 1980s, 2 folders (Box 44)
  - 1990s Executive Office Files Subseries, 1965-2001 and undated, bulk 1989-1999, 47 boxes
    The largest subcategory in the Executive Office Series, this subseries chiefly comprises files assembled and maintained during the tenure of Deborah Ross, the ACLU of NC's Executive Director during the 1990s, for some time also serving as Legal Director. Subdivided into Board Meetings and Issues Files, loosely according to the original Executive office's filing subdivisions.
    - Board Meetings, 1988-1992
      Minutes and agendas of ACLU of NC Executive Board meetings and Legal Foundation Board meetings, often mixed in one folder. Files usually contain many other materials relating to meeting agendas, including national office memos, reports, board guidelines and bylaws, requests for legal aid, testimony, and correspondence. Very often there are multiple meetings represented in one folder. Several of the board meetings are retreats, and several are from the annual board meetings, held in the spring. Meetings were held in cities such as Durham, Greensboro, and Chapel Hill. Some active Legal Foundation Board meeting participants are Robert M. Elliot (President, Newman, and Simpson (most documents only specify last name), and active Board of Director meeting participants are Moore, Newman, and Jim Fuller.
      The Legal Foundation Board meetings discuss fundraising, organizational growth, and progress on cases. Cases include the repeal of the NC Crimes Against Nature Statute (lesbian and gay issues) and the display of the Confederate flag (free speech issues). The Board of Directors meetings discussed budgeting, fundraising, personnel policies, and what cases to accept or reject. Proposed cases include issues of religious instruction in public schools, search warrants for an entire block, picketing the neighborhood and home of an abortion practitioner, educational equality, the War on Drugs, and AIDS. Arranged in chronological order. Other Legal Committee meeting files can be located in the Legal Program Series.
      - Board meetings, 1988-1990 (Box 45)
      - Board meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 46)
      - Board meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 47)
    - Issues Files, 1965-2001 and undated, bulk 1990s
      Identified as subject files assembled by Deborah Ross, the Executive Director during most of the 1990s, or by her assistants. Subjects range widely, with some folders containing material dating back to 1965, though most date between the late 1980s to the late 1990s. A large section (beginning at Box 83) consists of media files - clippings and news releases on particular subjects, in addition to files on the ACLU of NC's media relations guides and files). These resource files were used heavily in support of NCCLU activities, including the legal work with which Ross was involved - for a time she was also Legal Director. Arranged in original groupings as received: some in no apparent organizational order, others are in alphabetical arrangements (for example, beginning with Box 73).
      - Reproductive freedom and women's rights projects, 1982-1992, 5 folders (Box 48)
      - Free speech, tobacco advertising, 1975-1990 (Box 48)
      - Workplace, lifestyle discrimination, 1991-1992, 3 folders (Box 48)
      - Worker's rights, worker's bill of rights, clippings, 1977-1983 (Box 48)
      - Prison project,1993-1994 (Box 49)
      - Single-standard defense of civil liberties, Alan Reitman, 1987 Nov. (Box 49)
      - Strip search, Greensboro, 1994 May (Box 49)
      - ACLU job announcement (Box 49)
      - Lobby, NCCLU, 1965-1983, 16 folders (Box 49)
      - Lobby, NCCLU, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Lobby, NCCLU, 1984-1986 (Box 49A)
      - Legislature, 1989, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Fetal protection, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Choice, 1991-1992, 3 folders (Box 50)
      - State abortion fund, 1988-1990 (Box 51)
      - Public education, campus groups, 1992-1994, 2 folders (Box 51)
      - Guardians of Liberty, letters, 1993-1994 (Box 51)
      - Death penalty, 1994 (Box 51)
      - Worker's rights project, 1986-1994 (Box 51)
      - Drugs, decriminalization, testing, 1986-1993, 3 folders (Box 51)
      - Race, 1991-1994 (Racial Justice Act, affirmative action, and reparations), 9 folders (Box 52)
      - Police, abusive, 1989-1993 (Box 52)
      - ACLU history, 1989 (Box 53)
      - ACLU national board, ballots and biographies, 1992-1994 (Box 53)
      - Strossen, Nadine, 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Glasser, Ira, 1984-1992 (Box 53)
      - Privacy and technology, 1993 (Box 53)
      - Radical right, 1994 (Box 53)
      - School prayer and baccalaureate services, 1993 (Box 53)
      - School vouchers, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
      - Supreme Court, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
      - Privacy, 1975-1994 (Box 54)
      - Lobby, central file, 1994 (Box 54)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Act, 1994 (Box 54)
      - Whistleblower Protection legislative kit, 1994 (Box 54)
      - Guardians of Liberty, letters, 1994 (Box 54)
      - ACLU-NC, development history, membership, 1971-1994 (Box 54)
      - Art auction, ACLU fundraiser (Box 54)
      - Children's Rights Committee, 1995 (Box 54)
      - Educational Equity Committee (Box 54)
      - Gay and lesbian rights, 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box 54)
      - Taxpayer rights, Hackney, 1993 (Box 54)
      - Immigration, 1993-1994 (Box 54)
      - Redistricting Wake schools, 1991 (Box 54)
      - Voters rights, 1993-1994, 3 folders (Box 55)
      - Legislative committee, lobby, 1990-1991 (Box 55)
      - Censorship, Franklin High, Macon County, 1994 (Box 55)
      - War, 1991-1994 (Box 55)
      - Sexuality education, 1994 (Box 55)
      - Youth, 1991-1994 (curfews, dress codes, violence and TV), 3 folders (Box 55)
      - Postage discounts, 1992 (Box 55)
      - Charity checklist, 1988-1991 (Box 55)
      - Legal department (Box 55)
      - Consultants/reports, 1978-1987 (Box 55)
      - Presidents of the ACLU, 1994 (Box 55)
      - Religious rights, 1992-1993, 3 folders (Box 56)
      - Legal Committee, 1984-1992 (includes guidelines for acceptance of cases), 2 folders (Box 56)
      - Human Rights Committee, 1991-1994, folders 1-3 of 6 (Box 56)
      - Human Rights Committee, 1991-1994, folders 3-6 of 6 (Box 57)
      - Bernstein, Lori, 1985 (Box 57)
      - Gardner, George, 1975-1987 (Box 57)
      - Simpson, William, 1986-1990 (Box 57)
      - Schneider, Flo, 1981-1988 (Box 57)
      - Wheaton, Liz (Box 57)
      - Ross, Deborah (Box 57)
      - Landmines resolution, 1994 (Box 57)
      - Board list (Box 57)
      - Legal Committee, 1994 (Box 57)
      - Internet reading room (Box 57)
      - Suicide, privacy/autonomy, 1994 (Box 57)
      - Hart survey, 1994 (Box 57)
      - Public opinion, crime, 1987 (Box 58)
      - Privacy, 1988-1994, 2 folders (Box 58)
      - Drugs task force, 1991 (Box 58)
      - Office info, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Press releases (Box 59)
      - Projects (Box 59)
      - Shirley (Box 59)
      - 1st Amendment, 11 folders (Box 59)
        Includes indecent exposure and 1st Amendment report.
      - 1st amendment, 11 folders (Box 60)
      - Affirmative action, 4 folders (Box 60)
      - Drug loitering, Raleigh (Box 60)
      - ADA, 2 folders (Box 60)
      - AIDS/ HIV, 5 folders (Box 60)
      - Arts funding, Mecklenburg/ Guilford, 6 folders (Box 61)
      - Burke County adult entertainment ordinance (Box 61)
      - Separation of church and state/religious discrimination issues, Jonathan Hill, 3 folders (Box 61)
      - Civil Rights Act, recent developments in 1983 law, 1996, 4 folders (Box 61)
      - Courts, DA calendar control (Box 62)
      - Supreme Court term, 1996 (Box 62)
      - Supreme Court term, 1995-1996 (Box 62)
      - Supreme Court decisions (Box 62)
      - Religious freedom in courtroom cases, 1996 (Box 62)
      - Paul Palmeisano (Box 62)
      - Picketing in front of courthouse (Box 62)
      - Curfew and Title VI, 2000, 8 folders (Box 62)
        Includes several folders on Lumberton County curfew.
      - Drug tax assessment, issues, Goldsmith, 10 folders (Box 63)
      - Silvestri, Richard, 5 folders (Box 63)
      - DARE, 5 folders (Box 64)
      - Department of Motor Vehicles, 3 folders (Box 64)
      - Drug testing, Winston-Salem, 10 folders (Box 64)
      - Marijuana use (Box 64)
      - NC income tax seizure (Box 64)
      - Due process, speedy trial (Box 65)
      - Employment, 5 folders (Box 65)
      - Gay/Lesbian rights, 5 folders (Box 65)
      - Hate mail (includes photographic material) (Box 65)
      - Internet, censorship, pornography, 2 folders (Box 65)
      - Immigrants, 5 folders (Box 65)
      - Parole, 9 folders (Box 66)
      - Police, 5 folders (Box 66)
      - Political contributions, 2 folders (Box 66)
      - Campaign finance, Asian-Americans (Box 67)
      - Children's rights committee (Box 67)
      - Carolina patriots, Goldsmith (Box 67)
      - Sex offenders, 2 folders (Box 67)
      - BNA law week (Box 67)
      - 4th Amendment (Box 67)
      - Public duty doctrine and state tort act, 1998 (Box 67)
      - Grants (Box 67)
      - Prisoner religious complaints, 6 folders (Box 67)
      - Prisoners' legal services (Box 67)
      - Prisoners' rights, 16 folders (Box 68)
      - Public TV issues, 7 folders (Box 68)
      - Ten Commandments issue, 1996-2000, court documents, 21 folders (Box 69)
      - Ten Commandments issue, cont., 8 folders (Box 70)
      - Safelight, red light traffic cameras (Box 70)
      - School/student rights, 11 folders (Box 70)
      - Schools and student rights, 24 folders (Box 71)
        Contains multiple folders on dress codes, drug testing, school expulsions, searches, and vouchers.
      - Schools and student rights, free speech, 4 folders (Box 72)
      - Saylor v. Valles (Box 72)
      - Strategic Litigation Against Public Participation (SLAPP) suit, 1st amendment, 4 folders (Box 72)
      - Voting rights, 1994-1995, 2 folders (Box 72)
      - Welfare (Box 72)
      - Women's rights, 5 folders (Box 72)
      - Abortion: (Box 73)
        - RU-486 (Box 73)
        - Abortion (Box 73)
        - Parental notice laws (Box 73)
        - CLE Materials, 1995-2000, 2 folders (Box 73)
      - Abstinence (Box 73)
      - Alliance for good government, 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box 73)
      - Alternative schools and programs (Box 73)
      - Armstrong, Catherine, 89-038 (Box 73)
        Gerald Beaver, Sample PLDG/Research. 42 USC, 1983.
      - Attorney fees, cases, 2 folders (Box 73)
      - Attorney Fees Committee (Box 74)
      - Attorney General and superior court judges (ethics), 3 folders (Box 74)
      - Bar Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 74)
      - Bar Committee (Box 74)
      - Begging (Box 74)
      - Begging, First Amendment (Box 75)
      - Budget, 2001, 2 folders (Box 75)
      - Campaign Finance, 3 folders (Box 75)
      - Censorship info (Box 75)
      - Chavez v. Illinois State Police (Box 75)
      - Chewning School (Box 75)
      - First amendment, Law/Cases Re: Discovery (Box 75)
      - First Amendment Law (Box 76)
      - Constitutional rights, Durham, 1983, 3 folders (Box 76)
      - Correction and justice (Box 76)
      - Curriculum committee (Box 76)
      - Qualified immunity (Box 76)
      - Death penalty files:
        - Death penalty (Box 76)
        - Trial and post-conviction, 3 folders (Box 76)
        - Organizing against the death penalty (Box 77)
      - Districting, GA (Box 77)
      - DNA files:
        - SB165, 2001, 3 folders (Box 77)
        - DNA, 2 folders (Box 77)
      - Drugs and loitering files:
        - Ordinances (Box 77)
        - Drug loitering (Box 77)
        - Briefs/Cases, 1985-1996 (Box 77)
        - Briefs and cases (Box 78)
        - Fl. cases (Box 78)
      - Drug testing files:
        - 1988, 2 folders (Box 78)
        - Litigation (Box 78)
        - Drug testing, 2 folders (Box 78)
      - Due process, 2 folders (Box 78)
      - DWB, 1996-2000, 3 folders (Box 79)
      - EEOC, Technical assistance manual, ADA, 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Educating Our Children, Journal of Common Sense, 1999 (Box 79)
      - Eleventh amendment, govt. cannot be sued, 1983, Official/in development (Box 79)
      - Emergency contraceptives, 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Environmental education (Box 79)
      - Evidence (Box 79)
      - First Amendment files:
        - Rutan v. Republican Party (Box 79)
        - Hatch Act cases (Box 79)
        - Cases (Box 79)
        - Public forum cases (Box 80)
        - Picketing/marches (Box 80)
        - Content based restrictions (Box 80)
        - Privacy rights cases, various, 1989-1993 (Box 80)
      - Fourth Amendment Public buildings, cases, etc., ad. searches (Box 80)
      - Free exercise cases (Box 80)
      - Gangs, 1991 (Box 80)
      - Governor's Study Commission Report on NC Public Schools, 1968, 2 folders (Box 80)
      - Greensboro Chapter, 1994-1996 (Box 80)
      - Hate mail, 2000s (Box 80)
      - HIV/AIDS confidentiality (Box 81)
      - Immigrants' rights (Box 81)
      - In God We Trust (Box 81)
      - Indecent exposure, 2001 (Box 81)
      - Industrial commission (Box 81)
      - Juvenile justice files:
        - Juvenile justice and children's rights (Box 81)
        - 1991 (Box 81)
        - Section, 1997-2000 (Box 81)
      - Juvenile justice cont. (Box 82)
      - Key votes, 2001 (Box 82)
      - Law enforcement training (Box 82)
      - Law libraries (Box 82)
      - Lawyers (Box 82)
      - Legislative Senate bills, 1995, 3 folders (Box 82)
      - Lobbying (Box 82)
      - Long range planning committee, 1997 (Box 82)
      - Male academies, 1991-1992 (Box 83)
      - Media Files
        - General:
          - Media/Tips Relations (Box 83)
          - 1994-1997 Press Calls (Box 83)
          - Letters to Editor (Box 83)
          - Op Ed Project (Box 83)
          - Press Releases 1999 (Box 83)
          - Press Releases 1998 (Box 83)
          - Press Releases 1997 (Box 83)
          - National Press Releases (Box 83)
        - Clippings and Press Releases:
          - Affirmative action / Discrimination (Box 83)
          - Aids (Box 83)
          - Arts (Box 83)
          - Assembly freedom (Box 83)
          - Censorship (Box 83)
          - Children's rights (Box 83)
          - Crime rates (Box 83)
          - Crime victims (Box 83)
          - Death penalty (Box 83)
          - Drugs (Box 83)
          - Due process / Criminal justice (Box 83)
          - Environment (Box 83)
          - Freedom of speech (Box 83)
          - Gay rights (Box 83)
          - Guns (Box 83)
          - Housing/Homeless/Poor/Mentally ill (Box 83)
          - Immigrants rights (Box 83)
          - Police/Prisons (Box 83)
          - Pornography (Box 83)
          - Privacy (Box 83)
          - Religious freedom (Box 83)
          - Reproductive freedom (Box 83)
          - Students/Schools (Box 83)
          - Taxes (Box 83)
          - Voting rights (Box 83)
          - Workers rights (Box 83)
      - Media files, continued (Box 84)
        - General:
          - ACLU/ACLU-NC "Fax all timely news clips to Phill Cutts" (Box 84)
      - Miami street sweeps (Box 84)
      - Military law (Box 84)
      - Native American Marriage License, 2000, 3 folders (Box 84)
      - Negligence, prisoners' rights and suing state governments (Box 84)
      - North Carolina Volunteer Lawyers for the Arts (NCVLA), 1994-1997 (Box 84)
      - NCVLA Board Notebook (Box 85)
      - NCCLU: Executor of the Bill of Rights (Box 85)
      - NC Right to Life v. Leake (Box 85)
      - Oorman (Box 85)
      - Other state reform (Box 85)
      - Parental consent, teen health (Box 85)
      - Police abuse, dogs, 1992 (Box 85)
      - Policy, 1983 (Box 85)
      - Pornography (Box 85)
      - Pregnant women and alcohol abuse, 2 folders (Box 85)
      - Keeping pregnant and parenting teens in school (Box 86)
      - Prison, public education (Box 86)
      - Privacy (Box 86)
      - Private prison construct, 2001 (Box 86)
      - Qualified immunity (Box 86)
      - Race, 2 folders (Box 86A)
      - Reapportionment, 1991-1993, folders 1 of 5 (Box 86A)
      - Reapportionment, 1991-1993, folders 2-5 (Box 87)
      - Redistricting (Box 87)
      - Reproductive freedom (Box 87)
      - Richard Roe (Box 87)
      - Confederate flag, Durham student, 1988 (Box 87)
      - Guy/Rudd, time (Box 87)
      - Runoff primary (Box 87)
      - Runoffs, draft/paper (Box 87)
      - Schools (Box 87)
      - Schools, censorship (Box 87)
      - Searches and seizures cases, 1988-1994 (Box 88)
      - Search and seizure, 4th amendment, 2 folders (Box 88)
      - Senate bills, 1996 (Box 88)
      - Sex discrimination and school sports, 2 folders (Box 88)
      - Sex ed. info, final, 2001 (Box 88)
      - Sexual harassment and 1st amendment (Box 88)
      - Sexual harassment, 1995 (Box 88)
      - Stacey Bartley (Box 88)
      - Strip search cases (Box 89)
      - Supervisory liability, prisoners' rights, 1983 (Box 89)
      - Ten Commandments, 4 folders (Box 89)
      - UNC board of governors, voting rights (Box 89)
      - Volunteers, lay (Box 89)
      - Voting rights, folders 1-6 of 15 (Box 89)
      - Voting rights, folders 7-15 of 15 (Box 90)
      - War on drugs (Box 90)
      - War powers, 1990-1992 (Box 90)
      - West law (Box 90)
      - 11th amendment, state is not a person, Michigan, 1988 (Box 90)
      - Troubled youth program (Box 90)
      - Wiretapping (Box 90)
      - Women's rights, 1991-1996, 2 folders (Box 91)
- Legal Program Series, 1968-2006 and undated, 260 boxes
  The largest series in the collection comprises all administrative and case files assembled and maintained by staff affiliated with the ACLU of NC's legal arm, beginning from its earliest years of formation in the late 1960s, through the mid-2000s. Arranged in the following subseries, described more fully below: General Counsel Office (64 boxes); Case Files (128 boxes); Legal Committee (8 boxes); and Paralegal Files (60 boxes).
  To find specific content over many decades of files, keyword search strategies may prove useful; each case or subject folder typically uses key words to describe case or topic (e.g., prayer in school, discrimination, 1st Amendment, prisoners' rights, etc.). Several searches using different terms work best. A reference archivist is available for assistance.
  Personal names have been removed from many case file titles in this public, web-accessible collection guide. A full version is available to on site researchers from the library's paper collection files; also, names are present on folder titles in boxes. Researchers should be aware that privacy laws govern the use or publication of information in these files.
  - General Counsel Office Subseries, 1968-1980s, 64 boxes
    These earliest files were administered by the North Carolina Legal Foundation, the branch of the ACLU of NC that handled all litigation and legal investigations. The records belong chiefly to Norman B. Smith, General Counsel (later known as Legal Director), mixed in with other early legal directors (who often served at the same time as Executive Director). In addition to case files, to which the majority belong or are related, there are also administrative files, correspondence, conference files, and files on programs such as summer internships. In original alphabetical arrangements, or in order as received. Subdivided into these groupings: General Files, 1971-1974; Cases Closed, 1968-1974; Requests for Assistance, 1968-1973; General Counsel Prisoners' Rights Project, 1974-1975; and Cases Closed, 1975-1980.
    Researchers should be aware that privacy laws govern the use or publication of information in these files. As with other legal files, the names of the defendants and others in many cases have been redacted from this collection guide but are present on folder titles in the boxes.
    - General Files, 1971-1974
      - ACLU, 2 folders (Box 92)
      - ACLU Lawyer's Conference, 1973 (Box 92)
      - Agenda, meetings (Box 92)
      - Alcoholic rehabilitation (Box 92)
      - Anti-censorship (Box 92)
      - Anti-Discrimination Act (Box 92)
      - Anti-riot laws (Box 92)
      - Anti-Single Shot Law (Box 92)
      - Attorneys fees: payment of as condition of suspended sentence (Box 92)
      - Bail (Box 92)
      - Black Panthers (Box 92)
      - Chapters of NCCLU, general (Box 92)
      - Charlotte Chapter (Box 92)
      - Civil Rights organizations, general (Box 92)
      - Confessions and guilty pleas (Box 92)
      - Conscientious objectors (Box 92)
      - Consumer protection (Box 92)
      - Cooperating attorneys (Box 92)
      - Corporate banking resolution (Box 92)
      - Court appointed attorneys (Box 92)
      - Daly, George: miscellaneous, correspondence, briefs, etc. (Box 92)
      - Death sentence (Box 92)
      - Dress regulations (Box 92)
      - Financial matters (Box 92)
      - Flag desecrations (Box 92)
      - Ford, Captain Frederick W. (Box 93)
      - Greensboro Chapter (Box 93)
      - Greenville County Humane Society (Box 93)
      - Guilford County Humane Society (Box 93)
      - High Point Elections (Box 93)
      - Income tax (Box 93)
      - Inmate Grievance Commission (Box 93)
      - Jobs 1970: consortium agreement (Box 93)
      - Juvenile rights (Box 93)
      - Labor organization (Box 93)
      - Legal aid requests (Box 93)
      - Legislative program, 1973 (Box 93)
      - Long hair cases (Box 93)
      - Mars Hill College (Box 93)
      - Membership (Box 93)
      - Mental health (Box 93)